article-host.com 2013-08-05

# Article Deck - your Free Article directory, submit & find Articles- free Article directory

### Privacy Policy Overview

This Privacy Policy covers the ArticleDeck treatment of personal information that is recorded when you submit an article, or request an article via email. Other than the information requested in our online forms, no other information is collected from visitors to our web site.

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the ArticleDeck web site, nor does it extend to people that ArticleDeck does not employ or manage.

### Author Anonymity

ArticleDeck does not provide or guarantee author anonymity. Authors who wish to remain anonymous should either **NOT** complete the Author Profile in their member accounts **OR** complete it using a Pen Name.

Although discovering an Author's real identity is difficult if a Pen Name is used in submitting articles, there are several ways for that information to be found if the Author Profile is completed with your real name and identity details.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

ArticleDeck maintains your email address and other pertinent information in a secure database. Your contact information is never released or sold to any vendor, partner or outside agency. ArticleDeck, however, reserves the right to contact ArticleDeck members via email as deemed necessary. Such mailings will always include detailed unsubscribe information, providing members the option of removing themselves from future ArticleDeck mailings at any time.

### Security

Your email address information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to ArticleDeck staff.

### Information Collection

ArticleDeck collects minimal personal information when you request or submit an article. The only information collected in these instances is your name, email address, IP address and the date of your request or submission.

### Information Use

If you are ArticleDeck Author member, your use of our service constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a promotion service for your article(s). In exchange, ArticleDeck reserves the right to use the contact information collected during member registration to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to provide a free newsletter, to inform you of additions to ArticleDeck, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information on behalf of our partners or advertisers.

You may remove yourself from any or all of our mailings at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes a valid email address and unsubscribe link which you can use to remove yourself from future mailings. Should you encounter problems in this regard, contact us.

Spam complaints will result in membership termination.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

ArticleDeck may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change.

Author Articles

More From This Author

Amitech USA, Ltd. is a member of one the world's leading pipe technology and manufacturing companies. Â The Amiantit Group is an international organization with a track record of growth-orientated...

After the Attorney General of Massachusetts promulgated comprehensive regulations governing the advertising and sale of cigarettes, smokeless tobacco, and cigars, petitioners, a group of tobacco...

Petitioner sought to fill wetlands for beach front subdivision, which Rhode Island Coastal Resources Management Council rejected, ruling that the proposal did not satisfy the standards for...

Petitioner was ordered deported for his criminal record. No country would accept him and Cambodia did not have a repatriation treaty. He challenged his detention indefinitely as...

The Mushroom Promotion, Research, and Consumer Information Act mandates that fresh mushroom handlers pay assessments used primarily to fund advertisements promoting mushroom sales. Respondent...

Related Articles

Related Articles

Â  Most of the ladies dream to have long and voluminous hair which is believed to enhance the facial beauty. However, not all women have the time and patience to take care of long hair. Thus,...

Spain, April 28, 2013 - Â The Minister of Employment and the Economy of Castilla-La Mancha, Carmen Home, said that "the Government of Cospedal is working to make the pilgrimage of the Virgen de las...

Most people consider that the easiest way to work is to have your own firm. This may be true as long as we have the funding and the abilities required to lead. However, even if we are enjoying a fair...

Anyone looking for a living space property then what really matters is the property to match up with the style and taste of the investor. The very latest project of Mantri developer known to be...

Every businessman uses marketing strategies to stay ahead in the game in order to make profits.Â  They employ experts and professionals who concentrate on these ploys to increase brand awareness and...

Latest Articles

Latest Articles

While you would think that the plumbing system of your house must be working perfectly, this may not be the situation. Everything might be working well when suddenly your sink will produce backflow...

The only person that can easily answer all your plumbing issues is a plumber. You may be coming across various plumbing issues in your everyday life due to some or the other reason. It doesnâ€™t take...

Nowadays, even the most qualified IT professionals are not able to get good jobs due to the tough competition in this sector. Attaining a good job has also become difficult because of the rapidly...

Microsoft is one of the most reputed names in the IT world.Â Microsoft certificationÂ training is a course that provides special skills to the professionals in order to enable them to survive in this...

In order to succeed in life and for achieving better job prospects it is very important for you to do something different from what other people are already doing. There is intense competition in...

Most Read Articles

Most Read Articles

Mothers Day Poems Mother when you're not I regarÃ© with my tears oh mother! the garden the House and the yard malvones; It will be when your absence palpiten Geraniums and cry the gardenias and...

Creative issues always arise when businessmen visit banner printers for Banners and Signs New York. It is not uncommon for creative designers and business owners to come at loggerheads over...

Accidents at execute atmosphere are an work-related danger and sometimes expected. You can only wish they do not occur to you and take highest possible care that they don't; but you cannot wish them...

Hot, spicy and sizzling wallpapers of south Indian actresses have the potential to attract many an eyeball. Even when you are forced to work by your tight schedules and meetings just a glance through...
